(Sheldon:)All right.
(Sheldon:)Well, what should
we talk about?
(Amy:)I don't know. Just ask me
whatever comes to mind.
(Sheldon:)Very well.
(Sheldon:)I know you've been
seeing other men.
(Sheldon:)Have you had coitus
with any of them?
(Amy:)Man, I walked
right into that one.
(Leonard:)Next we need a
teaspoon of pepper,
(Leonard:)which, I believe, was also
the name of your childhood dog.
(Penny:)Fine. You think
you know so much.
(Penny:)Who's my favorite
Spice Girl?
(Leonard:)Baby.
Who's my favorite member of NSYNC?
(Leonard:)Justin.
Who's my favorite Backstreet Boy?
(scoffs): Nice try. NSYNC forever.
Damn it!
(grunts)
Face it,
(Leonard:)you can't stump me...
I am the king of husbands.
(Leonard:)I know that you
don't like the lingerie
(Leonard:)that I got you
on Valentine's Day.
I know you hate the word "moist." I know...
Hang on.
(Penny:)Wait, wait. Why don't I like
the lingerie you got me?
(Leonard:)Because it's orange
(Leonard:)and you think it makes you
look like a slutty carrot.